lottostrategies.com 2007-02-06

# Privacy Policy - LottoStrategies.com

|   
---  

|   
---  
  
LottoStrategies.com takes your privacy seriously. 

There are several components to our strict Privacy Policy. Our adherence to these principles ensures that your confidentiality is protected. 

**Information Gathering and Use**  
LottoStrategies.com collects only necessary personal information - such as your name, e-mail and address - when you sign up for account, and asks for no information we don't absolutely need to serve you. 

LottoStrategies.com also automatically records your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. This information helps us accomplish your requests, customize our content and advertising and serve you better. 

**Information Dissemination**  
LottoStrategies.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information in any manner not disclosed in this statement. Under no circumstances will LottoStrategies.com disclose your personal information to any third parties. 

**Lotto Forums**  
LottoStrategies.com has a message board available for visitors. Please keep in mind that any information disclosed in the Lotto Forum becomes public information. You should be cautious when decided to disclose any personal information. 

**Security**  
The sensitive personal information in your LottoStrategies.com account, such as your password, is password protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of the site, LottoStrategies.com uses industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions. 

| **Quick Lottery Reference**  
---  

[**District of Columbia(DC)** State Lotto Lottery Information,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/state_lottery_info/209/DC/dc-lottery.html) [Winning Numbers.](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/last_results/209/DC/dc-lottery-results.html) [District of Columbia(DC) Lottery Past Results,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_select_state/209/DC/dc-lottery-numbers-archive.html) [Hot Lotto,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/112/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Hot-Lotto-lottery-results.html) [DC Daily 6,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DC3/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-DC-Daily-6-lottery-results.html) [Midday 3,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DCA/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Midday-3-lottery-results.html) [Powerball,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/101/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Powerball-lottery-results.html) [Lucky Numbers,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DCB/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Lucky-Numbers-lottery-results.html) [Rolling Cash 5,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DC4/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Rolling-Cash-5-lottery-results.html) [Midday 4,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DCC/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Midday-4-lottery-results.html) [DC 4,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DCD/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-DC-4-lottery-results.html) [Hot 5,](http://www.lottostrategies.com/script/winning_of_past_month/100/DC2/DC/District-of-Columbia-DC-Hot-5-lottery-results.html)
